<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Segmentation on Rui Shen</title>
    <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/tags/segmentation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Segmentation on Rui Shen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sherry-sr.github.io/tags/segmentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Writing IOS App</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/write/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/write/</guid>
      <description>Practicing handwriting using the copybook of calligraphy is suffering because we usually don&amp;rsquo;t know how good we write and how much we can improve it. So we developed Master Writing to help people conquer it. Master Writing is an IOS application that helps people improve handwriting by showing how a master is writing and let people imitate it. Users can learn how to master different fonts by practicing writing letters, words and sentences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wavelet Based ROI-Preserving Medical Image Watermarking Scheme</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/watermarking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/watermarking/</guid>
      <description>This is my course project for Wavelets course. The motivition of this project is to utilize wavelets characteristics to address the privacy concern in medical image database system. During the course I was thinking if we can store sensitive patient information invisibly using wavelets watermarking technique. I designed my soluttion with the following features: non-ROI segmentation, ensure watermarking will never modify ROI parta sparse matrix generated by a private-key to determine the location of non-ROI modification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lip Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/lip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/lip/</guid>
      <description>This student project was conducted on 2016 at my junior year. It stemmed from one of my thoughts &amp;mdash; can we detect lip movements with micro-camera, transfer lip language to synthetic voice, thus enabling the mute to communicate just like us? we took 10000 photos of Chinese speakers speaking basic vowels, conducted automatic detection of faces and lips with OpenCV, and trained a neural network to recognize basic Chinese vowels. We built a lip language reader using Raspberry Pi and a camera with 92.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>