<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Rui Shen</title>
    <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Rui Shen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sherry-sr.github.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sub-thalamic nuclei Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/subtha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/subtha/</guid>
      <description>This is the current project I am working on. My ultimate task is to develop better segmentation and analysis methods for thalamic &amp;amp; sub-thalamic nuclei based on multimodal MRI such as DTI/DKI and MPnRAGE. I have been conducting some experiments including investigating several fiber tractography methods solving crossing fiber problem, visualizing multimodal data using TSNE and UMAP, investigating optimization tools for difffusion kurtosis claculation and the cause of error estimation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile C-arm Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/pose/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/pose/</guid>
      <description>This project&amp;rsquo;s object was to estimate the 6 degrees-of-freedom pose of the mobile C-arm imaging device based on a single image. The motivation of this work was to determine the best device position within limited X-ray shots in order to reduce unnecessary radiation exposure administered by the system. My work involved investigating different design markers by which to encode the device pose, and I decoding the pose through segmentation and registration methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Writing IOS App</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/write/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/write/</guid>
      <description>Practicing handwriting using the copybook of calligraphy is suffering because we usually don&amp;rsquo;t know how good we write and how much we can improve it. So we developed Master Writing to help people conquer it. Master Writing is an IOS application that helps people improve handwriting by showing how a master is writing and let people imitate it. Users can learn how to master different fonts by practicing writing letters, words and sentences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradigm Design for Grid Cell Study</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/grid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/grid/</guid>
      <description>Overview  This is my bachelor graduation project in 2016. Inspired by Bellmund&amp;rsquo;s paper &amp;ldquo;Grid-cell representations in mental simulation&amp;rdquo; published in August 2016, I was thinking if grid-like representations can be activated given more abstract and simple cues, and can be detected using fMRI. The motivation was to simplify the original experimental paradigm from the paper, in order to make it possible to use in wider clinical trails and measurements. In my graduation project, I first implemented the navigation task in virtual-reality city using Unity3D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lip Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/lip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/lip/</guid>
      <description>This student project was conducted on 2016 at my junior year. It stemmed from one of my thoughts &amp;mdash; can we detect lip movements with micro-camera, transfer lip language to synthetic voice, thus enabling the mute to communicate just like us? we took 10000 photos of Chinese speakers speaking basic vowels, conducted automatic detection of faces and lips with OpenCV, and trained a neural network to recognize basic Chinese vowels. We built a lip language reader using Raspberry Pi and a camera with 92.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aircraft Monitoring based on ADS-B</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/adsb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/adsb/</guid>
      <description>ADS-B (Automatic dependent surveillance—broadcast) is &amp;ldquo;a surveillance technology in which an aircraft determines its position via satellite navigation and periodically broadcasts it, enabling it to be tracked.&amp;rdquo; I worked on this student project with two friends when we were sophomores. We built an reliable aircraft monitoring system with 200km detection zone, based on ADS-B technology. We improved the performance of the receiver at 1090MHz by making an extensional coaxial collinear antenna ourself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>