<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matlab on Rui Shen</title>
    <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/tags/matlab/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Matlab on Rui Shen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sherry-sr.github.io/tags/matlab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wavelet Based ROI-Preserving Medical Image Watermarking Scheme</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/watermarking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/watermarking/</guid>
      <description>This is my course project for Wavelets course. The motivition of this project is to utilize wavelets characteristics to address the privacy concern in medical image database system. During the course I was thinking if we can store sensitive patient information invisibly using wavelets watermarking technique. I designed my soluttion with the following features: non-ROI segmentation, ensure watermarking will never modify ROI parta sparse matrix generated by a private-key to determine the location of non-ROI modification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrated vascular (iVas) MRI</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/ivas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/ivas/</guid>
      <description>Gas-inhalation magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) is a novel imaging technique to measure multiple brain hemodynamic parameters, such as cerebrovascular reactivity (CVR), cerebral blood volume (CBV), bolus arrival time (BAT) and functional connectivity (FC). This technique uses two physiological measures, specifically arterial CO2 and O2 time course, as input and BOLD MRI signal time course as output, and employs a linear model to determine the association between gas challenge and MRI signal, which is related to vascular properties of the brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradigm Design for Grid Cell Study</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/grid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/grid/</guid>
      <description>Overview  This is my bachelor graduation project in 2016. Inspired by Bellmund&amp;rsquo;s paper &amp;ldquo;Grid-cell representations in mental simulation&amp;rdquo; published in August 2016, I was thinking if grid-like representations can be activated given more abstract and simple cues, and can be detected using fMRI. The motivation was to simplify the original experimental paradigm from the paper, in order to make it possible to use in wider clinical trails and measurements. In my graduation project, I first implemented the navigation task in virtual-reality city using Unity3D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart Rate Monitoring from PPG</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/hht/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/hht/</guid>
      <description>This is a small prject I have been working on when I first joined Medical Electronics Laboratory in Southeast University. My task was to extract and analyze the real-time heart rate from PPG signals. I investigated Hilbert-Huang transform (HHT), short-time Fourier transform (STFT) and continuous wavelets transform (CWT) in this project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lip Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/lip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/lip/</guid>
      <description>This student project was conducted on 2016 at my junior year. It stemmed from one of my thoughts &amp;mdash; can we detect lip movements with micro-camera, transfer lip language to synthetic voice, thus enabling the mute to communicate just like us? we took 10000 photos of Chinese speakers speaking basic vowels, conducted automatic detection of faces and lips with OpenCV, and trained a neural network to recognize basic Chinese vowels. We built a lip language reader using Raspberry Pi and a camera with 92.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aircraft Monitoring based on ADS-B</title>
      <link>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/adsb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sherry-sr.github.io/projects/adsb/</guid>
      <description>ADS-B (Automatic dependent surveillance—broadcast) is &amp;ldquo;a surveillance technology in which an aircraft determines its position via satellite navigation and periodically broadcasts it, enabling it to be tracked.&amp;rdquo; I worked on this student project with two friends when we were sophomores. We built an reliable aircraft monitoring system with 200km detection zone, based on ADS-B technology. We improved the performance of the receiver at 1090MHz by making an extensional coaxial collinear antenna ourself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>